(Stuart:)You know something, Jesse?
(Stuart:)You may have a
successful business
(Stuart:)and the kind of pink complexion
that comes with good nutrition...
(Stuart:)But I have something
more important.
(Jesse:)-What's that?
-Friendship.
(Stuart:)Which I would trade in a
heartbeat for all of this.
(Howard:)The mineral and rock show?
(Howard:)That would be awful even
without Bert.
(Amy:)So what am I supposed to do now?
(Raj:)Prepare your uterus
for his gigantic offspring?
(Amy:)This isn't funny.
(Amy:)I'm gonna have to
(Amy:)that even if I didn't
have a boyfriend,
(Amy:)I wouldn't be interested in him.
(Howard:)I've heard those
words so many times.
(Howard:)From Linda Nosenchuck,
Tammy Rosenworcel...
(Raj:)Padma Kapur, Neha Chowdury...
(Howard:)Marci Grossman,
Lisa Mazzarino...
(Raj:)-Megan Pincus...
-Tammy Cho...
(Raj:)Who was that girl
from our Starbucks?
-Arlene Russell!
-Yes! Arlene!